Register of the Daniel Lerner collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1914-1949 (Boxes 67-87)
  - World War,., 1939-1945
    - German coastal defenses in the West (Folder 86: 3)
    - German Hochbunker (Folder 86: 4)
    - German war casualties (Folder 86: 5)
    - Humor and caricatures (Folder 86: 6)
    - Neutral countries. (Folder 86: 7)
      See also SUBJECT FILE/ Switzerland
    - Peace settlement, French view of Poland. (Folder 86: 8)
      See SUBJECT FILE/World War, 1939-1945/ Generalgouvernement
      - Prisoner of war camps in
      - Germany. (Folder 86: 9)
        See also SUBJECT FILE/World War, 1939-1945/Displaced persons
      - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (Folder 86: 10)
    - Propaganda
      - Allied
        - Bulletins
          - Die Brücke (Folder 86: 11)
          - Feldpost (Folder 86: 12)
          - Frontbrief zur Kriegslage (Folder 86: 13)
          - Frontline News-Letter (Folder 86: 14)
          - Frontpost (Folder 86: 15)
          - Luftpost (Folder 86: 16)
          - Nachrichten für die Truppe
            - ., 1943 (Folder 86: 17)
            - ., 1944 (Folder 86: 18)
            - ., 1945 (Folder 86: 19)
          - Votre France (Folder 86: 20)
        - Leaflets (Box 87)
          - Originals (Folder 87: 1)
          - German reports on (Folder 87: 2)
          - Studies regarding exposure of German civilians to (Folder 87: 3)
        - Newspaper (Folder 87: 4)
        - Pamphlets (Folder 87: 5)
        - Poster (Folder 87: 6)
        - Radio messages (Folder 87: 7)
        - Studies regarding Soviet propaganda (Folder 87: 8)
      - German
        - Bulletins (Folder 87: 9)
        - Leaflets (Folder 87: 10)
        - Pamphlets (Folder 87: 11)
        - Reports regarding (Folder 87: 12)
        - Slogans (Folder 87: 13)
  - Yugoslav nationality, Loss of Yugoslavia (Folder 87: 14)
    - ., 1944 (Folder 87: 15)
      Clippings and reports (in German and in Serbo-Croatian)
    - ., 1945 (Folder 87: 16)
- Declassified Records, 1949 (Box 87)
  Formerly security-classified records. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover.
  - 2011 September release of records, 1949 November 22 (Folder 87: 17)
    Stanford Research Center, "Estimating the Vulnerability of European Counties to Communist Subversion" project report.
- Photographs (Photo file)
  See Photograph Card Catalog